zypog.com 2017-12-16

# Free Prepaid Mobile recharge | Free online Recharge | Free Talk time

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Zypog.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by Zypog.com in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

### What information is or may be collected from you

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from:

-an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use  
-the domain server through which you access our service  
-the type of computer you're using  
-the type of web browser you're using

### We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:

name including first and last name  
\- email address  
-mobile phone number and contact details  
-demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation and education);  

We may also use your personal information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze our website usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our website's content and layout. We do this in an attempt to improve our website and better tailor it to meet our Users' needs. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. We will use your email address to contact you regarding administrative notices or latest news from time to time. We will use information in the file we maintain about you, and any other information that we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, in order to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems and to enforce our Terms and Conditions.

### Advertisers and 3rd Party Websites :

Zypog may offer some features where sometimes it is required to provide some of the information about you to a third party, which is offering such services. It must be understood clearly that we will provide information only to the extent that the said third party requires your information, which enables you to use their service, but prior to that we will make efforts to notify you of specific information being provided to such third parties. Before you use the services of any third party, we request you to check up and evaluate if the terms and conditions of said third party services are acceptable to you.

Zypog might use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

### Anti spam policy :

Any registered User of Zypog can send Forward SMS text messages to his/her friends & family. These interface conditions of use strictly forbid spamming to cell phone Users. We have several software filters to block spam messages. However, we cannot guarantee that spamming will not ever occur. Please let us know (email to help@zypog.com) the details of the message like content of message, time of delivery, sender name or number etc so that we can immediately check and block the user responsible for the same.

### Security :

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and email address, Mobile Number submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Your Zypog Account is password protected. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information and email address and Mobile Number, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

if you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at Help@zypog.com
